Guide to the International Brotherhood of Teamsters Brotherhood of Maintenance Of Way Employees Division records 1926-1999 IBT0045
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
IBT Brotherhood of Maintenance Of Way Employes Division records
1926-1999
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen, and Helpers of America
Brotherhood of Maintenance of Way Employees. Brotherhood of Maintenance of Way Employes. International Brotherhood of Teamsters. Brotherhood of Maintenance of Way Employes Division
IBT0045
5 Linear Feet
This collections contains the publications, constitutions, and by-laws of the Brotherhood of maintenance and Way Employees. The Brotherhood of Maintenance of Way Employes is a Division of the Rail Conference of the International Brotherhood of Teamsters representing and protecting the rights of rail workers who build and maintain the track and structures on railroads throughout the United States of America.The materials range in date from 1929 - 2014.
Arrangement
Organized into 2 series: Brotherhood of Maintenance and Way Employees Publications and Brotherhood of Maintenance and Way Employees Constitutions and By-Laws
Scope and Contents
Please note that the organization's name is not Brotherhood of Maintenance of Way Employees. The collection name correctly transcribes the organization's official title and reflects a spelling variant of employees acceptable in the 19th century when the organization was founded.
This collections contains the publications, constitutions, and by-laws of the Brotherhood of maintenance and Way Employees. The Brotherhood of Maintenance of Way Employes is a Division of the Rail Conference of the International Brotherhood of Teamsters representing and protecting the rights of rail workers who build and maintain the track and structures on railroads throughout the United States of America.The materials range in date from 1929 - 2014.
Conditions Governing Access
This collection is open for research.
Labor unions -- United States -- History -- 20th century; Labor and laboring classes; Labor unions; Labor
- Brotherhood of Maintenance of Way Employes Publications, 1926-1999; Series 1; 1.5 Linear Feet
  Arrangement
  Arranged alphabetically
  Scope and Contents
  This series contains the agreements between various companies and employees represented by the Brotherhood of Maintenance and Way. The dates of the material ranges from 1926-1996.
  - AFL-BMWE Membership Ballot and Recruitment Pamphlet, April 30, 1951; Series 1 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Agreement between Amtrak (National Railroad Passenger Corporation) and the Brotherhood of Maintenance of Way Employees, 1970-1976; Series 1 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Agreement between the Eastern and Western Carriers' Conference Committees and the Employes' National Conference Committee, Fourteen Cooperating Railway Labor Organizations, December 17, 1946; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Agreement-Brotherhood of Maintenance of Way Employes with the Ahley, Drew, and Northern Railway Company, November 1964; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Agreement Between The Baltimore And Ohio Railroad Company and All That Class of Employes Herein Specified, 1926-1952; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Agreement Between The Baltimore And Ohio Railroad Company and The Brotherhood of Maintenance Way Employees, 1930; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Agreement Between The Baltimore And Ohio Railroad Company and The Brotherhood of Maintenance of Way Employes, 1951; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Agreement Between The Baltimore And Ohio Railroad Company and The Brotherhood of Maintenance of Way Employes, 1951; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Agreement Between The Baltimore And Ohio Chicago Terminal Railroad Company and The Brotherhood of Maintenance of Way Employes, 1930; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Agreement Between The Baltimore And Ohio Chicago Terminal Railroad Company and The Brotherhood of Maintenance of Way Employes, 1966; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Agreement Between The Baltimore And Ohio Railroad Company and The Brotherhood of Maintenance of Way Employes, 1968-1979; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Agreement Between The Baltimore And Ohio Railroad Company and The Brotherhood of Maintenance of Way Employes, 1968; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Agreement Between The Eastern, Western, and Southeastern Carriers' Conference Committee and the Employes' National Conference Committee, Seventeen Cooperating Railway Labor Organizations, May 26, 1946; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Agreement Between The Baltimore And Ohio Railroad Company and The Brotherhood of Maintenance of Way Employes, 1968-1985; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Agreements between the Brotherhood of Maintenance of Way Employees and Bangor and Aroostook Railroad Company, May 1966-October 1996; Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Algoma Central Railway Rates of Pay and Rules, 1979-1980; Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Association of American Railroads-"The Human Side of Railroading", July, 1965; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - BMWE Division Ephemera, July 1966-June 2010; Series 1 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Agreement Between Bangar And Aroostook Railroad Company Canadian American Railroad Company And The Brotherhood of Maintenance of Way Employes, 1996; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Belfast And moosehead Lake Railroad Company Agreement With Employees, 1943; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Agreement Between The Bessemer And Lake Erie Railroad Company and the BMWE, 1921; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Bessemer and Lake Erie Railroad Company Roster Of Employees of the Maintenance of Way Deptartment, 1943; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Bessemer And Lake Erie Railroad Company - Rules Governing Employees of The Maintenance of Way Department, 1921-1922; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Bethlehem Steel Corporation-Pensions, April 1955; Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Brotherhood of Maintenance of Way Employees Agreement with the Atlanta and West Point Railroad Company, July 1977; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Agreement Between The best Railway Company of Chicago and The Employees, 1940; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Agreement Between Berlin Mills Railway and The Employees Represented by Brotherhood of Maintenance of Way Employes, Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Agreement With Employees in Track Department maintenance of Way Department Bostom and Albany R.R., 1921; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Boston and Albany Railroad Rules And Rates of Pay, 1945; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Brotherhood of Maintenance of Way Employees Agreement with the Board of Trustees of Galveston Wharves, September 1962; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Agreement Between Boston And Maine Railroad and the Brotherhood of Maintenance of Way Employes, 1951; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Boston And Maine Railroad Rules Governing Employees of the Engineering Department, 1942; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Agreement Between Boston and Maine Railroad And The Brotherhood of Maintenance of Way Employes, 1943-1951; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Agreement Between Burlington Northern Inc. And HS Employes Represented By The Brotherhood of Maintenance of Way Employes, 1971; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Brotherhood of Maintenance of Way Employees Agreements with the Burlington Northern Railroad Company, January 1966-September 1982; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Agreements between the Brotherhood of Mainenance of Ways Employees and Canadian National Railways, 1966-1998; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Agreements between the Brotherhood of Mainenance of Ways Employees and Canadian National Railways, 2001; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Agreements Between Canadian national Railway Company and Organizations Signatory Hereto, 1979; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Agreements between the Brotherhood of Maintenance of Way Employees and Canadian Pacific Limited, 1983-1986; Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Canadian National-"You and the CN Pension Plan" booklet, 1992; Series 1 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Central Vermont Railway, Inc. Agreement, 1941; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Agreements between the Brotherhood of Mainenance of Ways Employees and Chesapeake and Ohio Railway, April 1977; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Agreement Between The Chesapeake and Ohio Railway Company Pere Marquette District and Employees in the Maintenance and Way Department, 1949; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Agreement Between The Chesapeake and Ohio Railway Company and Employees in the Maintenance of Way Department, 1955; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Agreement Between The Chesapeake And Ohio Railway Company And Maintenance of Way Employees, 1955; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Agreement Between The Chesapeake And ohio Railway Company Southern Region And Maintenance of Way Employees, 1955; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Chessie System - Safety Rules, 1979; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Agreement Between the Chicago, Burlington, and Quincy Railroad Company and the Brotherhood of Maintenance of Ways Employees, 1933-1938; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Chicago Indianapolis and Louisville Railway Company, 1928; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Agreement Between The Chicago River and Indiana Railroad Company The Indiana Harbor Belt Railroad Company And Their Employees, 1968; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Agreement Between The Chicago, Rock Island and Pacific Railroad Company and the Chicago, Pock Island and Pacific System Federation Brotherhood of Maintenance of Way Employes, 1938-1971; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Agreement between Cleveland, Cincinnati, Chicago and St. Louis RY. Peoria and Eastern Railway Louisville and Jeffersonville Bridge and Railroad Co. and the Brotherhood of Maintenance of Way Employes, 1947-1954; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Agreement Between Clinchfield Railroad Company And Its Employees Represented By Brotherhood of Maintenance of Way Employes, 1964-1973; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Agreement between Clinchfield Railroad Employees Benevolent Association and Clinchfield Railroad Benevolent Association, March 1954; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Congressional Railway Review-100th BMWE Anniversary, 1987; Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Conrail, Inc.-Securities and Exchange Commission Filing and transactions, January 10, 1997; Series 1 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Cornwall Railroad Company, 1951; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Brotherhood of Maintenance of Way Employees Agreements with the Colorado and Southern Railway Company, Januar 1973; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Agreement Between Cumberland And Pennsylvania Railroad Company and the Brotherhood of Maintenance of Way Employes, 1942; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Delaware And Hudson Railway Company and Brotherhood of Maintenance of Way Employes, 1975; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Dennis Kurseth Correspondence and Media Articles, September-October 1981; Series 1 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Brotherhood of Maintenance of Way Employees Agreements with the Detroit and Toledo Shoreline Railroad Company, July 1955; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Brotherhood of Maintenance of Way Employees Agreement with the Detroit, Toledo, and Ironton Railroad Company, October 1962; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Florida East Coast Industries, Inc.-"Your Group Medical Plan" booklet and memorandum bulletin, February 1991-September 1995; Series 1 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Agreement between Fort Worth and Denver Railway Company and the Brotherhood of Maintenance of Way, August 1971-October 1973; Series 1 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Golden Spike: Clippings and Northwestern Pacific Rail Souvenir Booklet, June 1965-April 1969; Series 1 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Gulf Coast Lines Employees' Hospital Association: Charter and By-Laws booklet and Memorandum, September 1960-March 1961; Series 1 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Brotherhood of Maintenance of Way Employees Handling Discipline Cases and Claim and Grievance Handling Manuals, 1985; Series 1 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Brotherhood of Maintenance of Way Employees Agreements with the Housten Belt and Terminal Railway, April 1973; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Agreement Between The Huntington and Broad Top Mountain Railroad and Coal Company and Brotherhood of Maintenance of Way Employes, 1944; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - BMWE Division Journal, Vol. 121, January-October 2012; Series 1 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - BMWE Division Journal, Vol. 122, March-December, 2013; Series 1 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - BMWE Division Journal, Vol. 123, January-February 2014; Series 1 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Agreements between the Brotherhood of Mainenance of Ways Employees and Kansas City Southern Railway Company, May 1966; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Brotherhood of Maintenance of Way Employees Agreement with the Kansas City Terminal Railway, 1971-1974; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - BMWE Internal Revenue Service Audit-S00 Line System Division Memo and Report, 1987-1996; Series 1 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Brotherhood of Maintenance of Way Employees International Headquarters-Detroit, Michigan, July 1966; Series 1 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Legislative and Political Training Conference-Agenda and Handouts, June 15-19, 2009; Series 1 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Legislative and Political Training Conference-"1-Welcome to Washington D.C.", June 15-19, 2009; Series 1 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Legislative and Political Training Conference-"2-About the BMWE Division of IBT", June 15-19, 2009; Series 1 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Legislative and Political Training Conference-"3-U.S. House of Representatives", June 15-19, 2009; Series 1 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Legislative and Political Training Conference-"4-U.S. Senate", June 15-19, 2009; Series 1 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Legislative and Political Training Conference-"5-The Railway Labor Act", June 15-19, 2009; Series 1 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Legislative and Political Training Conference-"6-Tips on Lobbying", June 15-19, 2009; Series 1 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Legislative and Political Training Conference-"7-Lisa Kinard-IBT-The Legislative Process", June 15-19, 2009; Series 1 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Legislative and Political Training Conference-"8-Field Action Notes", June 15-19, 2009; Series 1 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - BMWED Lodge Leadership Video, undated; Series 1 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Local Lodge #289-News Clippongs and Correspondence, 1978-1983; Series 1 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - BMWE-Locomotive Engineers and Trainmen News, May 2004; Series 1 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Brotherhood of Maintenance of Way Employees Agreements with the Louisville and Nashville Railroad Company, April-October 1973; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Brotherhood of Maintenance of Way Employees Agreements with the MidLouisiana Rail Corporation, 1987; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Milestones of Progress: A Brief History of the Brotherhood of Maintenance of Way Employees, 1969; Series 1 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Minutes of the 15th Regular Convention: Nickel Plate Wheeling and Lake Erie Federation of the BMWE, September 29, 1997; Series 1 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Brotherhood of Maintenance of Way Employees Agreement with the Missouri-Kansas-Texas Railroad Company, September 1961; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Brotherhood of Maintenance of Way Employees Agreement with the Missouri Pacific Railroad Company and Employees Hospital Association, March 1953-November 1980; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Brotherhood of Maintenance of Way Employees Agreement with the Monongahela Connecting Railroad Company, June 1, 1964; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Brotherhood of Maintenance of Way Employees Agreements with the New Orleans Public Belt Railroad, January 1970; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Agreement Between The New York Chicago and St. louis Railroad Company The Lorain and West Virginia Railway Company And Its Employs, 1951; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Agreement Between The New York, Chicago And St. Louis Railroad Company and Its Represented By Brotherhood of Maintenance of Way Employes, 1951; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Massachusetts Bay Transportation Authority and New York, New Haven, and Hartford Railroad Company, July 1965; Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Brotherhood of Maintenance of Way Employees Agreements and Map of the New York, Chicago, and St. Louis Railroad Company-Nickel Plate Road, February 1951; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - MidLouisiana Rail Corporation Agreement with the Brotherhood of Maintenace of Way employees, August 1987; Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Agreement between the Brotherhood of Maintenance of Way Employees and New Jersey Transit Rail Operations, December 2000; Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - New York Central System-Funded Contributory Retirement Plan, November 1956; Series 1 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - New York Dock Railway-Interstate Commerce Commission Docket and "Face the State" Audio Commentary by William A. Thompson, February 23, 1979-May 8, 1983; Series 1 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Agreement Norfolk And Western Railway Company, 1962; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Northern Pacific Terminal Company of Oregon-Hospital Department Regulations and Surgical Benefit Plan, 1949-1979; Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Pennsylvania Railroad Company: Agreements, Safety Rules, and Supreme Court Petition, 1957-1962; Series 1 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Philadelphia and Reading Relief Association, 1942-1959; Series 1 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Agreement Between The Pitsburgh and West Virginia Railway Company and the Brotherhood of Maintenance of Way Employes, 1944; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Agreement Between The Pittsburgh And Lake Erie Railroad Company and Brotherhood of Maintenance of Way Employes, 1965; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Port Terminal Railroad Association, 1973-1978; Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Photographs, March 30, 1991; Series 1 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Brotherhood of the Maintenance of Way Employees Agreements with the Railway Association of Canada, 1974-1975; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Rates Of Pay And Rules Governing Services Of Maintenance of Way Employees, 1979; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Agreement between the Brotherhood of Maintenance of Way Employees and Richmond, Fredericksburg, and Potomac Railway Company, January, 1973; Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Brotherhood of Maintenance of Way Employees Agreements with the Spokane International Railroad Company, September 1965; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - St. Louis-San Francisco Railway Company-Conductors' Schedule, October 1, 1955; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Agreement and Interstate Commerce Commission Finance Docket for the St. Louis Southwestern Railway company, March 1980-January 1981; Series 1 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Brotherhood of Maintenance of Way Employees Agreements with the St.Louis-San Francisco Railway Company, 1951-1975; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Seaboard Coast Line Railroad company, 1968-1985; Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Brotherhood of Maintenance of Way Employees Agreement with the Southern Pacific Transportation Company, April 1960-April 1988; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Southern Pacific Railway System Retirement Plan, June 1953; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - BMWE-Teamsters Rail Conference Survey, May 13, 2009; Series 1 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Brotherhood of Maintenance of Ways Employees Agreement with the Terminal Railroad Association of St.Louis, September 1965; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Brotherhood of Maintenance of Ways Employees Agreement with the Texas-Mexican Railway Company, April, 1982; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Toronto, Hamilton, and Buffalo Railway Company Rules Governing Services of Maintence of Way Employees, January 1977; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Thomas W. McGuire Papers, 1955; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Track Motor Car Laws In Twenty-Five States, 1958; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - "Transition to the Future"-Second Regular Convention: Official Program, June 21-23, 2010; Series 1 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - "Transition to the Future"-Second Regular Convention: Quadrennial Report, June 21-23, 2010; Series 1 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - "Transition to the Future"-Second Regular Convention: Bylaws Committee Report, June 21-23, 2010; Series 1 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - "Transition to the Future"-Second Regular Convention:Resolutions and Credentials Committee Report, June 21-23, 2010; Series 1 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - "Transition to the Future"-Second Regular Convention: Miscellanous Committee Reports, June 21-23, 2010; Series 1 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - "Transition to the Future"-Second Regular Convention: Daily Proceedings, June 21-23, 2010; Series 1 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - "Transition to the Future"-Second Regular Convention: Miscellanous-Teamsters Rail Conference, June 21-23, 2010; Series 1 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Brotherhood of Maintenance of Way Employees Union Shop Agreement-Railway Labor Employes National Committee, September 1952-August 1954; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Union Pacific Railroad Agreements andd Memorandum, February 1987-November 2001; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Brotherhood of Maintenance of Way Employees Agreement with the Upper Merion and Plymouth Railroad Company, September 1962; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Brotherhood of Maintenance of Way Employees Wages and Working Conditions Contract with the Colorado and Wyoming Railway Company, August 1975; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Westinghouse Air Brake Company-Repair Track Maintenance Leaflet, No.2389 Sup.1, January 1956; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Green Bay and Western Railroad Company Agreement with The Employees Represented by the Brotherhood of Maintenance Way Employees, June 1, 1974; Series 1 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Soo Line Railroad Company Agreement with The Brotherhood of Maintenance Way Employees, August 14, 1987; Series 1 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Minnesota Transfer Railway Company Agreement with The Brotherhood of Maintenance Way Employees, February 1, 1952; Series 1 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Reprint - Washington Job Protection Agreement of May 1936, December 1968; Series 1 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Improved Medicare for All, Undated; Series 1 (Box Shared Box 35, Folder 13)
  - Labor Campaign for Single-Payer Healthcare, 2013, 2016; Series 1 (Box Shared Box 36, Folder 18)
- Brotherhood of Maintenance of Way Employes Constitutions and By-Laws, 1949-1970; Series 2; 0.5 Linear Feet
  Arranged chronologically
  This series contains the constitutions, by-laws, and rituals of the Brotherhood of Maintenance and Way employees. One constitution, and one ritual booklet are in French. Date range 1949=1970.
  - BMWE-Allied Eastern Federation By-Laws and Constitution, August 1997; Series 2 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Constitution And By-Laws of the Brotherhood of Maintenance Of Way Employes, 1949; Series 2 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Constitution And By-Laws of the Brotherhood of Maintenance Of Way Employes, 1952; Series 2 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Constitution And By-Laws of the Brotherhood of Maintenance Of Way Employes, 1958; Series 2 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Constitution And By-Laws of the Brotherhood of Maintenance Of Way Employes, 1958; Series 2 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - By-Laws Governing the Pennsylvania Federation of the Brotherhood of Maintenance of Way Employes, 1963; Series 2 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Constitution et Reglements de la Fraternite Des Preposes Au Maintien Des Voies Ferrees, 1966; Series 2 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - By-Laws of the New York Central System Division of the Brotherhood of Maintenance of Ways Employees, June, 1958; Series 2 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - By-Laws For the Government of the Northeastern Regional Association of the Brotherhood of Maintenance of Way Employes, 1967; Series 2 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Constitution and By-Laws of the Brotherhood of Maintenance of Way Employes, 1970; Series 2 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Constitution and By-Laws of the Brotherhood of Maintenance of Way Employes, 1974; Series 2 (Box 4, Folder 1)